export const verbPracticeDataEllinika = {
  2: [
    { prompt: "Εγώ", answer: "είμαι" },
    { prompt: "Εσύ", answer: "είσαι" },
    { prompt: "Αυτός", answer: "είναι" },
    { prompt: "Αυτή", answer: "είναι" },
    { prompt: "Αυτό", answer: "είναι" },
    { prompt: "είμαι", answer: "εγώ" },
    { prompt: "είσαι", answer: "εσύ" },
    { prompt: "είναι", answer: "αυτός/αυτή/αυτό" }
  ],
  3: [
    { prompt: "Εγώ", answer: "έχω" },
    { prompt: "Εσύ", answer: "έχεις" },
    { prompt: "Αυτός", answer: "έχει" },
    { prompt: "Αυτή", answer: "έχει" },
    { prompt: "Αυτό", answer: "έχει" },
    { prompt: "έχω", answer: "εγώ" },
    { prompt: "έχεις", answer: "εσύ" },
    { prompt: "έχει", answer: "αυτός/αυτή/αυτό" }
  ]
};
